

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science Multimedia and Animation Technology Mahanakorn University of Technology 2016 - 2018

Diploma in Information
Technology
Intrachai Commercial College
2013 - 2015

#### **SKILLS**

- Python
- PySide/PyQt
- PostgreSQL/MySQL
- SQLAlchemy
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- JSON
- Git GitHub/GitLab
- Linux bash/tcsh

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Thai
- English

# **APISIT SENLUANG**

## Python Developer

- apisit.senluang@gmail.com
- **\** +66 85-990-2957
- 199/135 The Connect 53, Kanchanaphisek Road, Thap Chang Sub-district, Saphan Sung District, Bangkok 10250.

#### **ABOUT ME**

A former 3D Animator who shifted to Pipeline Developer, passionate about technical problem-solving. I'm a quick learner who eagerly enjoys new challenges. My experience working closely with artists and the team has enhanced my communication and collaboration abilities.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Pipeline Engineer

2022 - 2024

The Monk Studio Co. Ltd.

My Responsibilities in the Pipeline Engineer Role:

- Data Management: Ingesting, organizing, and packaging files.
- Tools: Building custom tools using Python and PySide2.
- **Database:** Experienced in using PostgreSQL for both direct SQL queries and the SQLAlchemy ORM framework.
- **Maintenance:** Fixing bugs, supporting users, and optimizing systems for efficiency.
- Infrastructure: Collaborating with IT on infrastructure issues.
- **DCC Integration:** Developing pipelines for DCC software E.g. Maya, RV, Nuke, Houdini, Blender.

#### **3D Animator**

2021 - 2022

#### Lap Production Co. Ltd.

Animate 3D characters and props in Maya. Automate repetitive tasks using Python scripting. Create a simple pipeline for media review and delivery to reduce errors and ensure consistency using Python with PyQt framework.

## 3D Animator (contract)

2019

#### World Learning Hub Asia Pacific Co. Ltd.

Create 3D Characters in Character Creator, animate it in iClone and paint textures using Blender